Sun Yao.
You killed her.
How could I bear to kill her?
I liked her so much.
I could not love her enough.
She flirted with me first.
Why are you taking a picture of me?
I'm so sorry.
I just thought your outfit looked nice.
I wanted to send it to him for reference.
If you mind, I'll delete it right away.
It's okay. I appreciate the compliment.
You're really nice, sir.
Thank you.
You're quite handsome.
I do not get it.
I am just an old man.
Why take pictures of me
and send them to you?
Does it mean I am more handsome than you?
You are jealous, right?
Feeling bitter, huh?
You're just scum!
Yes.
I am scum.
Let me tell you,
that year we came up with a new scheme.
Which was
to set up
someone by collecting their information.
And then,
we would set up a scam targeting them.
For example, telling that person
that we had caught their family member,
and kill the hostage if they did not pay.
You know what?
It was such a coincidence.
The first scheme was used on Sun Yao.
It was just that coincidental.
Her mother lost her phone,
and her brother took a trip without his.
Oh, right.
If you were her fiancé,
what were you doing back then?
What were you doing?
By pure coincidence,
it was just perfectly timed.
Sun Yao could not reach anyone.
I sent her the doctored photo.
She saw her mother's blood-covered face,
and broke down on the spot.
Begging me to let her mother go.
So pathetic, do you not think?
Well?
Does it sound
like a familiar story?
I am a very kind-hearted person.
I will not keep you in suspense.
I will tell you the rest of the story.
If you do not want your mother to die,
do exactly as I say.
Okay, I'll do whatever you say.
I transferred the money to you guys.
Please don't hurt my mom.
I have sent a location to your phone.
Go there now to pick her up.
Call police, and we will kill the hostage.
Okay.
Who are you?
Where's my mom?
What did you do to her?
Do not be afraid.
Your mother is fine.
As long as you do as I say,
she will be okay.
Put the mask on.
Change into these clothes.
Go.
I won't do it.
I knew it.
You would not listen to me.
I treat you so well.
Why can you not see my true feelings?
What do you want?
I will not force you.
Just behave and cooperate.
Do not push me.
I'm begging you.
I gave you the money.
I'm getting married soon.
Please let me go.
Please!
Getting married?
That makes me even more excited.
You are marrying me.
Let me go! Let me go!
Why... why is it you?
Don't touch my woman!
Do not be afraid.
Stay back!
If you come any closer, I'll jump!
Careful.
You are not going to jump.
Do you not like me?
Who would like a psycho?!
You do not like me.
You flirted with me first.
That day,
you secretly took photos of me
and called me handsome.
But when I came to you,
you ignored me.
I want to ask you.
You call me a psycho.
Are you the psycho, or am I?
Answer me.
I'll die before a psycho like you wins!
No!
Clean up the scene.
Do not let the police find any clues.
Yes, sir.
What a pity.
Bastard!
If you don't kill me, I'll kill you!
Kill me, huh?
Keep dreaming.
How will you kill me?
With your eyes?
Let me tell you,
I am leaving the country soon.
As if you could.
Take a look.
Does she not look like Sun Yao?
Heaven has been too good to me.
Actually, I think
it is a real pity that Sun Yao died.
But Heaven gifted me another one,
a woman who looks exactly like her.
What do you think? Do they look alike?
Well, do they?
Do they?
What are you going to do to her?
Of course, before I leave,
I will make her completely mine.
But do not worry.
Before you die,
I will let you take one last look at her.
Look!
Beat him.
Feel free to get creative.
Just do not kill him.
Yes, sir.
Gu Ting, please do not worry.
We are doing all we can to find him.
Captain Sun.
At the hospital, you called me Yao Yao.
Who is Yao Yao?
This is my sister, Sun Yao.
She was also Li Wen's fiancée.
Two years ago,
Yao Yao fell victim to a scam syndicate
and passed away.
So,
Li Wen approached me
because I look like Sun Yao,
and my father might be a fraud suspect.
At first,
Li Wen just wanted Gu Yan
to help him infiltrate the scam syndicate.
But he did not know you looked so alike.
So I am not anyone's stand-in.
And I am not some bait.
I am Gu Ting.
The person I want to save
is the man who clearly hates my father,
yet still risked his life to save me.
Yaoyao...
How could you...
How could you be so foolish?
Yaoyao.
I promise I will bring Li Wen back safely.
I haven't reached Li Wen for days.
Could something have happened to him?
Did he go after Yan for revenge?
Right. I have the private line he left me.
Gu Ting.
Do you need something?
Hello?
Mr. Yan.
I really don't know what to do.
That's why I called you.
Calm down.
By the way,
how did you get my number?
You gave it to me before.
You said it was my private line.
Mr. Yan,
my dad is really a scammer.
I handed the evidence to the police.
That is putting justice before family.
I really don't know what to do anymore.
My boyfriend broke up with me over this.
Strangers kidnapped me all day yesterday.
I feel like I can't go on anymore.
Do not do anything rash.
You only have one life.
Do not do anything foolish.
Mr. Yan, the school said you took leave.
Where are you?
You're the only one I can rely on now.
I am recovering in a remote place.
I will send a car to pick you up.
Thank you, Mr. Yan.
You're so kind.
Wait for me.
Okay.